Before becoming a professional hairstylist, I had no idea there was even a difference between curling irons.
I'm Laura Gibson, beauty expert here to tell you the different between curling irons.
There's three types.
One would be your chrome curling iron, your gold curling iron and your ceramic curling iron.
Now the different between the three, varies.
For example, the first one which everyone usually likes to go because it will save you a penny, that would be your chrome.
The second one is more for someone who uses their flat iron but not everyday, that would be your gold.
Now however, if you're a curling iron junkie like me, you're going to want to what?
You're going to want to go with ceramic.
Ceramic actually seals your cuticle to leave you with that silky smooth finish.
So once again, there are three types of curling irons.
Chrome, gold and ceramic.
Its all about what you want.
I'm Laura Gibson, beauty expert.